ILGWU. Research Department records 5780/123
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Monthly Bulletin, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Monthly Bulletin, 1942-1945 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1949-1950 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Daily Label Sales, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members [folder 1 of 2], 1947-1950 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Bulletins Sent to Members [folder 2 of 2], 1947-1950 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meetings and Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board: Meetings and Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry: Meetings and Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Legal, 1907-1912 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Legal: Lubin Testimony, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Legal, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Legal, 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Legal: Appellate Court of Illinois [folder 1 of 5], 1917 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Legal: Appellate Court of Illinois [folder 2 of 5], 1917 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Legal: Appellate Court of Illinois [folder 3 of 5], 1917 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Legal: Appellate Court of Illinois [folder 4 of 5], 1917 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Legal: Appellate Court of Illinois [folder 5 of 5], 1917 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Legal, 1918-1920 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Legal, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Legal: Joint Appendix, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Legal [folder 1 of 2], 1922 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Legal [folder 2 of 2], 1922 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Legal, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Legal, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Legal: Appellate Court of Illinois [folder 1 of 3], 1925 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Legal: Appellate Court of Illinois [folder 2 of 3], 1925 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Legal: Appellate Court of Illinois [folder 3 of 3], 1925 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Legal, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Legal, 1929-1931 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Legal: Supreme Court Dubinsky versus Joseph Love Incorporated, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 11)